Have you ever made a promise to yourself that you didn’t keep?
你是否曾对自己许下承诺，最后却没能遵守？
Commonly, when the new year ticks over, we make resolutions: going to the gym, studying harder or giving up a bad habit.
通常，每当新年钟声敲响，我们都会立下新年决心：去健身房锻炼、更努力学习或是戒掉某个坏习惯。
Sadly, not long after we’ve made the promise, we often end up breaking them.
遗憾的是，许下诺言后没过多久，我们往往就会违背它。
But what if you want to create a new good habit?
但如果你想养成一个新的好习惯呢？
Well, it’s possible, but willpower might not be the only thing you need.
这并非不可能，但意志力或许并非你唯一需要的东西。
The basic idea of a habit is something we do almost unconsciously, as if you’re on autopilot.
习惯的本质，是我们近乎无意识、如同自动驾驶般做出的行为。
An example of this would be having breakfast or saying ‘please’ and ‘thank you’.
比如吃早餐、说“请”和“谢谢”，这些都是习惯。
Good habits can be part of your daily routine.
好习惯可以成为日常生活的一部分。
But if we don’t have those habits, how can we create them?
但如果我们本身没有这些习惯，该如何养成呢？
According to a study published by the European Journal of Social Psychology, it takes an average of 66 days to form a new habit.
根据《欧洲社会心理学杂志》发表的一项研究，养成一个新习惯平均需要66天。
However, relying only on determination may not be the answer.
不过，只靠决心可能并不够。
Questioning why you want something to be the norm rather than relying on your resolve could be the key.
关键或许在于，问自己为何想让某件事成为常态，而非单纯依赖决心。
Do you want to lose weight because you want to be healthier or feel more attractive?
你想要减肥，是为了更健康，还是为了让自己看起来更有魅力？
The issue is, willpower could be subject to your mood – a bad mood may mean you don’t want to do something.
问题的关键是，意志力会受情绪影响——心情不好的时候，你可能就不想去做既定的事了。
You should also avoid trying to change too much at once – remember that it’s a case of baby steps.
你还应该避免试图一蹴而就——要记住，凡事都要循序渐进。
Giving up all your favourite foods, going to the gym, and stopping drinking at the same time will probably result in failure rather than sustainable practice.
一下子戒掉所有爱吃的食物、坚持去健身房锻炼、同时还戒酒，这样做很可能会失败，而非形成可持续的习惯。
And don’t worry about failing – just start again!
而且别害怕失败——大不了重新开始！
Finally, don’t do things outside your comfort zone.
最后，不要做超出自己舒适区的事。
If you hate mushrooms, don’t persevere and try to add them to your diet just to be healthier.
如果你讨厌蘑菇，就不要为了健康而勉强自己吃。
Eat something you like!
吃一些自己喜欢的食物就好！
It might not be quick, but if you follow these tips, you may be able to change something for the better or kick a bad habit.
这个过程或许不会一蹴而就，但只要遵循这些建议，你或许就能做出积极的改变，或是戒掉某个坏习惯。